{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [{
        "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Board%20Games",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "How%20many%20spaces%20are%20there%20on%20a%20standard%20Monopoly%20board%3F",
        "correct_answer": "40",
        "incorrect_answers": ["28", "55", "36"]
    }, {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "How%20many%20Hz%20does%20the%20video%20standard%20PAL%20support%3F",
        "correct_answer": "50",
        "incorrect_answers": ["59", "60", "25"]
    }, {
        "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What%20is%20the%20age%20of%20Ash%20Ketchum%20in%20Pokemon%20when%20he%20starts%20his%20journey%3F",
        "correct_answer": "10",
        "incorrect_answers": ["11", "12", "9"]
    }, {
        "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20company%20did%20Bethesda%20purchase%20the%20Fallout%20Series%20from%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Interplay%20Entertainment%20",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Capcom", "Blizzard%20Entertainment", "Nintendo"]
    }, {
        "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20element%20does%20the%20Zinogre%20use%20in%20Monster%20Hunter%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Thunder",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Ice", "Fire", "Water"]
    }, {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which%20RAID%20array%20type%20is%20associated%20with%20data%20mirroring%3F",
        "correct_answer": "RAID%201",
        "incorrect_answers": ["RAID%200", "RAID%2010", "RAID%205"]
    }, {
        "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20character%20does%20the%20player%20play%20as%20in%20the%20video%20game%20%22Bastion%22%3F",
        "correct_answer": "The%20Kid",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Rucks", "Zulf", "Zia"]
    }, {
        "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20film%20did%20James%20Cameron%27s%20Avatar%20dethrone%20as%20the%20highest-grossing%20film%20ever%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Titanic",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Star%20Wars", "Gone%20with%20the%20Wind", "Jaws"]
    }, {
        "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20Zelda%20games%20did%20not%20feature%20Ganon%20as%20a%20final%20boss%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Majora%27s%20Mask",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Ocarina%20of%20Time", "Skyward%20Sword", "Breath%20of%20the%20Wild"]
    }, {
        "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Comics",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which%20pulp%20hero%20made%20appearances%20in%20Hellboy%20and%20BPRD%20comics%20before%20getting%20his%20own%20spin-off%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Lobster%20Johnson",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Roger%20the%20Homunculus", "The%20Spider", "The%20Wendigo"]
    }]
}